Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is milk and cookies. Let me show
you how to make it. In your pint, you're
going to combine 400 g of a fat-free
high protein milk, some sweetener, some
zantham gum, a little bit of salt, and
some vanilla bean paste. If you don't
have paste, just use extract. It's the
same thing. And then, of course, you're
going to freeze your pint for at least
16 hours. Take it out, run under hot
water for about a minute, and then throw
in your creamy on the light ice cream
setting. It'll probably come out looking
something like this. Kind of powdery, so
we can just scrape down the sides. And
while we do that, we can also hollow out
a hole in the center and add our mixins.
If yours is very powdery, I would respin
it before doing this. And then throw
your lid back on and throw it back in on
the mixing setting. And then all that's
left to do is top it with your protein
cookie dough bites. And you are good to
go. Drop a comment if you want me to
make some other Ben & Jerry's flavors or
Dairy Queen Blizzard flavors. I'll do
the most like comment.